

ABOUT ME

I am eager and have willing to work as a team, hard worker with excellent health. I am able to operate computer and have good command in English both speaking or writing. Experienced in handling

customer queries with friendly and professional approach. Thrive in fast-paced environments, ensuring customer satisfaction through clear communication and problem-solving. Excel in building rapport and resolving issues efficiently.

CONTACT ME



+359 87 9582333



alyanovita698@gmail.com



💡 ul.Bregalnitsa 65 Sofia, Bulgaria 1303

ALYA NOVITA EFFENDI

EDUCATION

INTERNASIONAL PROFESSINAL INSTITUTE

2020 - 2022

Certificate Of Higher Education Hospitality

LANGUAGE

Indonesian - Native

English - Conversational

French - A1

SKILLS

Hospitality understanding

Teamwork

MS Office

EXPERIENCE

Customer Relation - Futures Brokerage Company

2022 - 2023 Bandung, iIndonesia

• organized and delivered presentations to potential clients, Remained updated on company offerings through regular product research

Housekeeping - Hyatt Regency Sofia

2023 - current Sofia, Bulgaria

Accurately managed guest room inventory for establishment rooms.